class Color():
    """Represents an RGB color.

    Represents a color with red, green, and blue components. Color objects
    can be tested with the == operator; if their components are equal, they
    are considered equal.

    Attributes:
        r: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the red component of
          the color.
        g: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the green component of
          the color.
        b: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the blue component of
          the color.
    """
    def __init__(self, r, g, b):
        """Initializes a new Color.

        Sets initial values for the attributes of a new Color instance.

        Args:
            r: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the red
              component of the color.
            g: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the green
              component of the color.
            b: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the blue
              component of the color.

        Returns:
            None
        """
        self.r = r
        self.g = g
        self.b = b

    def __eq__(self, other):
        """Tests for equality of two Color instances.

        Compares the color components (R, G, and B) of two Color instances
        to determine if the instances represent the same color.

        Args:
            other: A Color instance to compare.

        Returns: True if the two colors are the same, False otherwise.
        """
        return (self.r == other.r
                and self.g == other.g
                and self.b == other.b)

    def as_tuple(self):
        """Creates a tuple of color components.

        Creates a tuple with the red, green, and blue components of the
        Color instance as elements.

        Args: none

        Returns: A tuple with the components.
        """
        return (self.r, self.g, self.b)

class ColorWithAlpha(Color):
    """Represents an RGB color with an alpha value.

    Represents a color with red, green, and blue components and an alpha
    value. ColorWithAlpha objects can be tested with the == operator; if their
    components and alphas are equal, they are considered equal.

    Attributes:
        r: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the red component of
          the color.
        g: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the green component of
          the color.
        b: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the blue component of
          the color.
        a: A float in the range [0.0, 1.0] representing the alpha value of
          the color.
    """
    def __init__(self, r, g, b, a):
        """Initializes a new ColorWithAlpha.

        Sets initial values for the attributes of a new ColorWithAlpha
        instance.

        Args:
            r: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the red
              component of the color.
            g: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the green
              component of the color.
            b: An integer in the range [0, 255] representing the blue
              component of the color.
            a: A float in the range [0.0, 1.0] representing the alpha value
              of the color.

        Returns:
            None
        """
        super().__init__(r, g, b)
        self.a = a

    def __eq__(self, other):
        """Tests for equality of two ColorWithAlpha instances.

        Compares the color components (R, G, and B) and alpha values of two
        ColorWithAlpha instances to determine if the instances represent the
        same color.

        Args:
            other: A ColorWithAlpha instance to compare.

        Returns: True if the two colors are the same, False otherwise.
        """
        return super().__eq__(other) and self.a == other.a

            
